overbestmall.com 2009-12-14

# Privacy

### Privacy Policy

**Background**

We recognize that you care how we use and share information about you. This Privacy Policy was created to tell you how the information related to you will be collected, used, shared and protected.

This Privacy Policy only applies to information gathered by us through this Web Site and our Customer Service Department in connection with this Web Site. We are not responsible for any information you reveal or post in public forums on any website.

By using this website, you accept this Privacy Policy. For further questions, you should contact our Customer Service Department through email or online service.

**1\. What information about customers is collected and stored?**

**We collect Personal Information and Non-Personal Information on this website. Personal Information includes:**  
The information we collect on this website to identify or contact customers, such as full names, street address, e-mail address, telephone numbers, credit card numbers and credit card expiration dates. The personal information are all offered by customers when they open accounts, place orders or contact Customer Service. These information is only used for the purpose described in this Privacy Policy.

**Non-Personal Information includes:**  
The information we collect on this Web Site that is relating to the use of this website, such as demographic information and other anonymous statistical data. This information is used to analyze and improve this Web Site and to optimize our customers' experience.

**2\. How do we use and share information?**

We only use the Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for the purpose we describe in this Privacy Policy, and we promise not to share any customer's Personal Information with others without customers permission.

We may share the Personal Information with third parties who offer services such as payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, order fulfillment and shipping, marketing and promotional material distribution, Web site evaluation, but we will only allow them to use the information connected to the services they offer.

We may release Non-Personal Information to our marketing partners and advertisers in order to improve our website's quality and customers experience.

**3\. How do we protect customers' Personal Information?**

We use various security measures, including Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology, to protect personal information that we collect on the website. If a customer wants to register as our website member, email address and password are needed in order to create and log in a customer account. Customers should be careful about providing order information to others. If a customer forgets his/her account password or becomes aware of any loss, theft or unauthorized use of his/her account, or needs to correct order information, he/she can contact our Customer Service Department by email or online service. 

**4\. Others**

**a.** You can update certain personal information through account management dashboard. 

**b.** If you come to our website through links on other websites, we are not responsible for the information you offered to other websites you come from.

**c.** Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be post on this website. We may also send you emails about the changes.
